KAZUKI MINEMURA

Email: kazuki.minemura@gmail.com, Mobile: +60-164741072

COMPUTER VISION ENGINEER

Computer Vision Engineer with over 5+ years of experience in Computer Vision / Deep leaning model development and algorithm validation to improve product capabilities, and Computer Scientist with over 10+ years of research experience. Extensive experience in the development and validation of computer vision algorithms. Passionate to share computer vision challenges and cutting-edge algorithms with the team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programing LanguagePython, C/C++, MATLAB, typescript, VBADeep learning frameworkOpenVINO, Caffe, Tensorflow, PytorchDevelopment toolJira, HSDES, Jenkins, Ansible, docker, git, vim

Web frameworkAngular, TornadoData Modeling/ManagementJson, XML, MongoDB

Typesetting Tex, Latex

Operating system GUN/Linux, MS Windows, Yocto BSP

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Intel Microelectronics (M), Penang, Malaysia Computer Vision Engineer

Jan 2019 - Present

- Lead a **multi-view classification & object detection** project with 2 members.
- Lead a validation and benchmark team with 5 members.
- Lead development of summary dashboard, reporting over **6k test cases** on 9 algorithms across multiple backends (CPUs, GPUs, VPUs).
- **Standardize execution** by Ansible, Docker, Jenkins framework, self-develop scripts.
- Manage CV/DL component validation projects, including test cases and execution.
- Actively join weekly technical analysis and discussion on deep learning & IoT trends.
- Educate new employees for ramping-up technical skills.
- Interview new employee candidates for hiring.
- Technical support for customer engineers & customers.

Software Validation Engineer

Jan 2018 - Dec 2018

- Test code development and automation. Achieved **5x work efficiency** as a team.
- Development & fine-tuning object detection model for lidar signal.
- Paper submission & Oral presentation at an international conference.
- Keynote speaker at a IPIARTI Symposium.

Graduate Trainee

Jun 2016 - Dec 2017

- Analyzing deep learning technologies and trend and weekly sync with in(ex)ternal teams.
- Lidar object detection model development.
- Weekly research sync with team and external collaborators.
- Object detection demo for internal company events.
- Autoware document translation from Japanese to English.

KAZUKI MINEMURA

Email: kazuki.minemura@gmail.com, Mobile: +60-164741072

EDUCATION

Ph.D in Computer Science

Feb 2013 - Jan 2017

University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Research title: Sketch An investigation into feature extraction in compressed domain
- 2 ISI indexed journal articles, 1 book chapter, 8 peer viewed conference papers.

M.S in Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Apr 2010 - Mar 2012

Shinshu University, Nagano, Japan

B.S in Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Apr 2006 - Mar 2010

Shinshu University, Nagano, Japan

PUBLICATIONS (Last 6 years)

ISI Indexed Journal

- J1. Raphaël C.-W. Phan, Yin-Yin Low, KokSheik Wong, **Kazuki Minemura**, "Strengthening speech content authentication against tampering". Speech Communication. Vol 6. 2021, (IF 2.017)
- J2. **Kazuki Minemura**, KokSheik Wong, C.-W Phan, Kiyoshi Tanaka, "A novel sketch attack for H.264/AVC format-compliant encrypted video". IEEE Transactions on Circuits and Systems for Video Technology. Jul. 2016, (IF 9.9)
- J3. **Kazuki Minemura**, KokSheik Wong, Xiaojun Qi and Kiyoshi Tanaka, "A Scrambling Framework for Block Transform Compressed Image," Multimedia Tools and Application, Feb. 2016, (IF 2.313)

Peer Reviewed Conference Paper

- C1. **Kazuki Minemura**, Hengfui Liau, Abraham Monrroy and Shinpei Kato, "LMNet: Real-time Multiclass Object Detection on CPU using 3D LiDAR", IEEE Conference on Intelligent Robot Systems (ACIRS), pp. 28-34, 2018.
- C1. Yiqi Tew, **Kazuki Minemura** and KokSheik Wong, "HEVC selective encryption using transform skip signal and sign bin", Asia-Pacific Signal and Information Processing Association (APSIPA), pp. 963-970, 2015.
- C2. Masaya Moriyama, **Kazuki Minemura** and KokSheik Wong, "Moving Object Detection in HEVC Video by Frame Sub-sampling," IEEE International Symposium on Intelligent Signal Processing and Communication Systems (ISPACS), pp. 48-52, 2015.